Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
And so?
And so.
I'm sitting there staring at him. right?
He tells me to get my crunchy
fucking fucknuts the fuck out of there.
You believe that shit?
- You know what I said. right?
- No. what did you say?
- Shit. "Okay."
- You fucking said. "Okay."
I'm sure you did.
Control Center.
this is Stillwell 1215.
Go ahead. Stillwell 1215.
I'm about four cars
out of 57th Street station...
...being delayed
by a red signal light.
Should be green. Stillwell 1215.
Yeah. tell me something
I don't already know.
All right. roll through it slow.
extreme caution. per the rulebook.
Yeah. cracked rail. Nine-hundred feet
from the east end of the platform.
It's the goddamn cold.
Metal contracts. you know that.
I got it. I got it.
How long it take to fix it?
Gotta put a plate on it. Two hours.
Thank you. Make it an hour and a half.
I'll buy you a beer.
Shit. G.B. I hate to see you
down here on the floor. man.
Temporary. baby. I'll be up there
behind the glass before you know it.
I'm gonna need the R train...
...to switch over
to the express tracks at 34th.
- Which express tracks?
- The one that Q uses.
Once they exit the 57th Street.
they can switch over to the F Line.
Straight into Queens.
Once they get to Queens. they switch
back at 36th Street to the R Line.
All you gotta do. suspend the W.
N and R will pick up the slack.
I can't see where I gotta look.
Unlock the door.
Do it now or I'll kill you. Do it.
All right. all right.
Shut up and walk.
First car. go.
See? I told you I could do this.
Big fucking deal.
you did what you said you'd do.
All right.
Five minutes of peace.
- Yeah!
- Nice!
- Nice.
- All right.
There you go.
I'm on the train and I still got you.
- You still got me?
- I got you. What are you doing?
You still got me?
Oh. my God.
Baby? Baby?
Give me the cutting key.
Cutting key.
Control Center calling Pelham 123.
Come in. Pelham 123.
Why did you stop?
You're all green ahead.
Control Center calling Pelham 123.
Why did you stop. 123?
You got green ahead.
It's okay.
Life is simple now.
You just gotta do what I say.
Not now. okay?
Where are you from?
- Brooklyn.
- You Irish?
Yeah.
I thought so.
Who's driving Pelham 123?
Maybe something fell on the tracks.
Wait. Are we going backwards?
42nd Street tower.
I got a train wrong-railing...
...on the southbound Lexington
Avenue Line just north of you.
Listen up.
we need to stop and stay in-station.
All southbound locals
just north of the 51 st Street station.
The operator on 123
is Jerry Pollard.
I know Jerry Pollard.
I went to motorman school with Jerry.
Pelham 123.
come in to me. Pelham 123.
Pelham 123. Jerry Pollard.
what's going on down there?
This is Control Center.
What's going on. 123?
Get an express train to go alongside
them. see what we see in the cab.
Yeah. this is South Ferry 105. I can't
get my windshield wiper to turn on.
South Ferry 105. there's a circuit
breaker right behind you for that.
What's going on?
Maestro. what's going on?
- Cop.
- Excuse me.
- Fuck.
- Watch your backs. Watch your backs.
When I say stop. stop it hard.
- Transit Police.
- Stop.
Everybody sit the fuck down!
Down!
Sit the fuck down!
Jesus! We're getting reports
of gunshots down the tunnel.
Sergeant Moran.
- Delgado. let's call off that express.
- Got it.
I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna fucking die. man.
Come on! Hey.
Everybody up! By the window!
Come on. up. up. up!
Stand up! Stand up! Come on!
Move it! Against the window!
What the fuck is going on?
There was a cop. Bashkin shot him.
I think... I think he's dead.
Put Bashkin on
and find your fucking guts!
- Do it!
- Fuck.
- What happened?
- A cop. He's dead.
Put the conductor on.
- What's your name. conductor?
- Regina.
Regina. baby. listen.
you got a job to do. honey.
A job?
God put you on this Earth
for one thing and one thing only.
You conduct those people
off the train...
...up to the platform.
You got that? Let me hear it.
Let me hear you do that.
Listen up. everybody.
We're gonna go back to the platform.
I need everybody to...
Regina. Let's do it again.
Conduct those people.
Listen. Now. we're gonna head back
towards the platform.
I want everybody to slowly get up.
- I'm gonna get you off this train.
- Good.
Now. we're gonna be on the tracks.
so if you don't need it. leave it.
Have been put on alert regarding...
Right here. right here.
Cross right here. right here.
- Go.
- Cross over right here. right here.
Let's go.
- Up the stairs. up the stairs.
- Here you go.
- Every cop in the city is on the way.
- Maybe it wasn't gunshots.
Train could be blowing breakers.
Or the motor blew?
No. this is on purpose.
Fuck you.
- Yeah. I'm coming.
- Get the fuck off the walls.
Shut the fuck up and come on.
Shit. Come on.
Ramos.
Turn the power off from there down.
What?
Turn the power off from there down!
Okay. I got it!
My fucking lucky day.
Shit.
What the fuck is wrong with you. man?
Pelham 123 to Rail Control Center.
Do you read me?
Yes. I read you. Pelham 123.
This is Control Center. Who is this?
It's me. man. I didn't wanna call
till everything was ready.
- It's not Jerry.
- I don't know who it is.
I understand. I understand.
Pelham 123.
Who the hell is this?
This is the man
who's gonna rock this city.
This is the man who's gonna
give the city a run for the money.
Look up. Look up at your screen
and you tell me what you see.
You see what I've done?
I see it.
One car is much more manageable
than 10 with the manpower I got.
Motorman's gonna tell you
about it. Tell him what we got.
They got hostages. lots of them.
- And they got machine guns.
- That's Jerry.
- Yeah. that's right.
Check me.
do you understand that?
I check. I understand.
Didn't I tell you to knock first?
Good. because this is what we call
a cash transaction.
Now. you understand commodities.
don't you?
You know. pork bellies?
Gold? Light crude?
Listen. no disrespect. but maybe I'm
not the guy you should be talking to.
Oh. no. you are exactly the guy
I wanna talk to.
Now. I want you to look at the ticker
and you tell me...
...what is the going rate
for a New York City hostage today?
You think a million dollars
is too much? I do. I think it's corny.
Now get your calculator out.
You got one?
- Do you have a calculator?
- Yeah. we got one. I got one.
Okay. good. Add this up.
You got $526.315 and 79 cents.
That's 526.315. 79.
Now. times that by 19.
What do you got?
What is he. a goddamn accountant?
- That's 10 million?
- What do you got?
That comes out to 10 million
plus one cent.
That is a deal.
You call the mayor
and you tell him the price.
And then you tell him I want it in
100.000 $ 100 bills. you got that?
I got it. What about the one cent?
Keep that. that's your broker fee.
Now. I want the rest
in plain suitcases...
...the kind with the wheels
and the portable handle. okay?
Now. this is not a futures contract.
This is a spot trade.
That means there's a time limit on it.
Okay. you got that?
Now. what do you think
is a fair time limit?
You know. I don't know.
I'm really just a guy...
Come on. give me a time limit.
Give me a fair time limit.
- Thursday.
- I was thinking more like an hour.
Now. what's your watch say?
Two-thirteen.
Oh.
that's exactly what my watch says.
So at 3:13. I want that money here.
motherfucker.
And after that. there is a late fee.
What do you think
that late fee is gonna be?
Come on. tell me what it'll be.
You're gonna kill the passengers?
Oh. commodities
is what I start to kill.
One for every minute
past the deadline I am forced to wait.
They become more valuable
this way...
...and still at the same price.
He's underground.
He's never gonna pull this off.
- Don't tell me. tell him.
- Who the hell is this guy?
- I don't know who it is!
- Garber. just stay with it.
What's your name?
- What's your name. my man?
- My name?
What's your name?
Tell him?
- Garber.
- Garber. okay.
Now. seriously. man.
in 59 minutes...
...I'm gonna start killing passengers.
So my advice to you is to get on
the phone. get the mayor notified now.
Listen. I mean...
I'm just a civil-service employee.
I can't get ahold of the mayor.
That's your problem. not mine.
It's like. who's responsible for
who lives and who dies in New York?
That's New York City's problem.
Get the fuck off the radio
and notify the mayor. motherfucker!
Okay.
Nine months of this and I'm free.
Next mayor gets inaugurated...
...I'm gonna be in Saint-Tropez
on the beach with a piña colada.
I will never have to ride the subway
ever again.
- Never say never. sir.
- Never.
All right.
what's next for the afternoon?
East Harlem Elementary at 2:30.
You're to read
The Cat In The Hat to the third grade.
Every time I go to the schools.
I get sick. They all have runny noses.
Call Dr. Katz. tell him I want him
waiting at the school. with a flu shot.
Mayor's office.
- He's in Car 3.
- Yeah.
What happened?
Somebody just hijacked a 6 train.
It's stopped in the tunnel
between 51 st and 42nd.
Another idiot with a gun.
What do we know?
It's unclear. but I have a car
waiting for us downstairs.
Subway will get us there faster.
All right. Let the doors close.
Tell them we'll meet them
at 59th Street.
Tell the conductor
this is now an express.
- We're skipping the next five stops.
- What?
- I gotta get to work.
- Hold on. hold on.
Everybody will get where they
need to go. we'll make all the stops.
Maybe he's not such a douchebag
after all. huh?
Funny.
Figures you'd be the one
to get a call like this.
Hostage negotiation team here in five
minutes and the mayor's been notified.
- You gonna tell him?
- Get the fuck out of here.
My shift's over in 10 minutes.
- What are you staring at?
- Your face.
I'm trying to remember
for when it's not here.
- You gonna start in on me?
- Right. I'm gonna start in on you.
- Don't fuck this up. Garber.
- You wanna do it?
It's your station. your call.
- Oh. it's my call now?
- That's right. Your call.
Come on.
Pelham 123. come in. this is
Rail Control Center. Are you there?
Gerber Baby boy. What's up?
Garber. Just wanted to let you know
the mayor's been notified.
Are they gonna pay?
I don't know. I'm just the.
what'd you call me? The broker.
No. no. you represent
the city of New York right now. buddy.
I can tell you you're dealing with one
of the all-time bureaucracies. I know.
- I mean. it takes time.
- You'd better fix the bureaucracy...
...because when the time comes.
these hostages...
...are gonna go real quick.
You got it. you got it.
Any other demands?
Yeah.
no fucking pizza for them. either.
No. I mean. are you guys. like.
you know. are you terrorists?
Do I sound like a terrorist?
Do I terrorize you?
Actually. you don't. but I mean.
not that I ever talked to one.
So...
So. what. this is just about money?
Oh. is there anything else?
There's not dying.
Yeah. well. you live. you die. You
go with the current or you fight it...
... you all end up
in the same place.
- Where's that. Jersey?
- Yeah. you watch it. I was born there.
I'm just saying.
you're up in the motorman's cab.
That means you're on the radio. which
means that you're an easy target.
You gotta know the drill.
I know that soon I won't be alone...
...and if I'm the first to get shot.
I'm the first of many to get shot.
That's correct.
but then you'd still be dead.
Dead is an improvement on a lot
of things I can think of. buddy boy.
Sounds like he slept with my ex.
You know. we all owe God a death.
And I'm a man who pays his debts.
Are you a man who pays his debts?
Yeah. yeah. sure.
TV. cable. and my mortgage.
- That's a little like dying once a month.
- You're married. you're a married man.
Maybe.
No. no. no. You're married. man.
Married men have mortgages.
You got a mortgage?
I don't know. Why don't you tell me.
then we'll both know?
I don't know. I'm sure someone
out there loves you dearly and...
... you know.
would be worried about you.
You're in the motorman's cab...
... you got no cover.
sniper on the way.
Well. you know.
circumstances are my protection...
...because right now. you know.
hostages are good insurance.
By the way I see it.
I'm pretty well-protected.
You know. this reminds me
of being in a confessional.
Are you Catholic?
I'm married. you're Catholic.
- Maybe. I don't know.
- No. you're Catholic.
And a good Catholic...
...would know he's got
a trainload of innocent people.
You don't wanna
kill innocent people. do you?
A good Catholic
knows that nobody is innocent.
And I'm not gonna kill all these
hostages. I'd give up my leverage.
Well.
I hope you know what you're doing.
It's running like a fucking Swiss watch
down here. so don't worry about it.
So. what do I call you anyway?
Call me Ryder.
As in "train rider"?
Call me Ryder. with a Y.
Ryder.
I like you. Garber.
I do like you. man.
You may be
the last friend I ever make.
Well. I hope you're wrong. Mr. Ryder.
But. you know. I'm just a guy.
I'm just a guy
on the other end of the mic.
Oh. you don't think
this was meant to be?
You don't think this was fate.
you and me?
I don't know. Things happen
that lead to other things.
And maybe this was one of them.
but that's it.
I never get excited
about coincidence.
Well. you got 50 fucking minutes.
so check me.
All right. 50 minutes. check.
And don't call me
unless you got news.
- You got it.
- Motherfucker.
G.B.
You're fucking good. man.
Okay. Move it the other way.
All right. come on. move it.
The other way.
Okay. now move it back a little less.
Bingo. Got it.
All right. we got it.
- Who's talked to these jokers?
- That would be me.
Yeah. under my supervision.
Who are you?
Vincent Camonetti.
NYPD Hostage Negotiation Team.
John Johnson.
Chief Transportation Officer.
Walter Garber.
I'm Console Dispatch. right now.
What can you tell me. Walter?
His name is Ryder. with a Y.
And he's asking
for $ 10 million by 3:13.
Looking toward the future. Say what
he'd do if he doesn't get the money?
He said he'd kill a passenger
every minute we go over.
- Starting at 3:13 p. m.?
- 3-1-3. yes. sir.
- Anything else?
- He's smart.
If he's smart. why is he doing
something so fucking stupid?
- On the train radio?
- We can get him right here.
Any chance that we can get
a signal down there?
We'd like to get him
on one of our cells.
No.
there's no chance. not where he is.
What's this?
"Leverage. spot trade"?
Yeah. it's weird. He's like
a money guy. like a Wall Street.
He talked about the passengers
like they were commodities.
- "Catholic"?
- Yeah. I think he's Catholic.
For chrissakes. Garber. you gonna tell
us what his zodiac sign is now?
I'm just saying I think he's Catholic.
Man asked me about "Catholic."
I wrote it down. I'm giving my opinion.
Unlike other people.
I have an opinion.
Fellas. can we settle
this dispute later?
- Absolutely.
- Why do you think he's Catholic?
I think he's Catholic because he talked
about original sin and confessions.
I wrote it down.
I didn't know what else to do.
- Did he ask for a priest?
- No.
Good. Anything else?
He sounded. the way he was talking.
he sounded like he's not afraid to die.
Yeah. well. it's early yet.
- The calls are coming through...?
- Right here.
You hit the blue button.
you can reach him.
- He'll come back to you.
- Mind if I take your seat?
- No. no. go right ahead.
- Thank you. Walter.
You're welcome.
This is the six wire.
You don't have to touch that one.
- Okay.
- That goes around the room.
- Six wire.
- Why don't you...
Just hit the talk here
and then that mutes it.
Take the rest of the day off.
Get out of here.
I thought I'd stick around.
just make sure that...
Well. that wasn't a suggestion.
So why don't you go home?
All right.
This is it. You got all the information
over here about the 313.
- Wait for his call.
- You want me to work it up right now?
You call headquarters. let them know
that I'm here and I'm on the job. Okay.
I gotta take a piss.
So who's stopping you?
All right. We wouldn't wanna end up
on any Amnesty International lists...
...so step up to the door. face out.
Open the middle door.
Do what you gotta do.
Can I jump down there?
- You gotta go or don't you?
- I do. I gotta go.
Step up. my man. Let's go. let's go.
That kid's going places.
All right. close the doors.
Pelham 123. come in.
- Pelham 123. please come in.
- All right. everybody. sit down!
Who is this?
This is Lieutenant Camonetti. I'm with
the NYPD Hostage Negotiation Team.
I'd like to talk to you
about the situation that we're in.
Where the fuck is Garber?
Mr. Garber is a train dispatcher.
- This is now a police matter.
- Yeah. well. I wanna talk to Garber.
I'm sorry. Mr. Ryder.
but Mr. Garber is no longer involved.
Motorman. up!
- Put Garber on.
- To be honest...
...Mr. Garber has gone home.
Put Garber on the fucking line
or I kill the motorman.
I guarantee you I am the best person
for you to be talking to right now.
Give me a moment
and I'll explain why.
You were always
gonna be the first one to go.
Oh. Jesus!
Jesus.
Mr. Camonetti...
...you got 60 fucking seconds
before I kill another.
- Okay? Fifty-nine. 58. 57...
- Get him. Just get Garber.
- Fifty-six. 55. 54...
- We're trying to locate Garber...
...ASAP. Mr. Ryder.
Why did you do that?
Mr. Camonetti or whatever
fucking greaseball name you got...
...the city of fucking New York
killed Jerry. okay?
Fifty-three. 52. 51...
Garber. Garber!
Garber. he killed Jerry Pollard. man.
Come on.
he wants to talk to you right now.
He's here. He's on the way.
Eleven. 10. nine. eight. seven...
- He's approaching the desk.
- Six. five. four. three. two. one...
Hey. it's me. it's Garber.
Garber! You didn't say goodbye.
You killed Jerry?
No. the city of fucking New York
killed Jerry. okay?
The biggest rathole
in the world fucking killed Jerry.
Okay? Now you can
chalk another victim up to NYC.
- Now. can everybody hear me?
- Yeah. we hear you. loud and clear.
Now you don't have to tell
the cops...
...they don't tell me how to do it or how
it's gonna be. I fucking tell them.
Don't you ever. ever
leave me again.
Or I'll just have to hunt you down
and I'll kill you.
Now. you got 39...
Thirty-nine minutes. Check me.
Thirty-nine. check.
This is Staley to ESU 2.
What's your position?
ESU 2 approaching hostage car
from south tunnel.
Go. go. go.
Ten-million dollars. I'll write him
a check and get it over with.
- He wants it in cash.
- I was joking. LaSalle.
But we've been given one hour
to get the money together.
Ten-million dollars.
Where do they get these numbers?
Actually. 10 is the limit. sir.
Why is that?
Request to the City Controller.
he forwards it to one of our lenders...
...cash gets released to the Federal
Reserve. Limit at any time is 10 million.
Some idiot with a gun
wouldn't know that. I didn't know.
- Well. you're very busy. sir.
- How do you know that?
Here he is.
- Henry. what's the situation?
- They killed a hostage.
These guys may be the real deal.
I thought there was one idiot
with a gun.
Multiple gunmen. They're not sure.
They've got 18 hostages.
They'll kill more in an hour. That's
the limit. They want you to know.
- What do we know?
- Not amateurs.
They cut out a car.
stopped on a rise.
They can see us coming
100 yards either way.
How long to get the money?
- I don't know.
- Find out.
- You're not thinking of paying. are you?
- I'm thinking of time and being ready.
Call the Controller.
Tell them we'll pay.
What's with you and Garber. huh?
Tell me about him.
Scheduled to work today?
- Yeah. absolutely. But...
- But what?
He's only had this particular job
for a couple weeks now.
- Well. why is that?
- Well. he's under investigation.
What?
- We were gonna suspend him...
- What's he being investigated for?
He went to Japan. He had to take
a look at some new trains...
...and the allegation
is that he took a bribe.
Took a bribe?
Does he have a record?
- Not that I know.
- You sure?
Yeah. yeah. I don't think so.
I gotta take this.
The identity of the hijackers
is still unclear.
The Hostage Negotiation Team has
just arrived at MTA headquarters...
... to determine
if this is a terrorist enterprise.
Is that what we are? An enterprise?
We're an enterprise.
Well. pilot reports
that the aircraft has begun its descent.
This is Staley to ESU 4.
What's your ETA?
Approximately two minutes
south of target.
Why is the train called
Pelham 123?
Comes out of Pelham Bay
at 1:23 in the afternoon.
How did you end up with this call?
It's a Lexington Avenue train.
I got the Lexington Avenue desk.
Came through my desk.
Can you think of a reason
why you'd be targeted?
Someone wanna hurt you?
Something against you or something?
No.
You recognize his voice?
No. No. as I said. it was a coincidence
it came through my desk.
Did you pick this desk?
Or was it assigned to you?
Did I...?
I said. did you pick this desk
or was it assigned to you?
Can I take my coat off?
Doesn't make any sense.
- What doesn't?
- Guy you're talking to.
He ain't a train dispatcher.
Walter Garber.
- He's a big shot.
- Big shot at what?
Rail Control.
I mean. he runs things up there.
- At least he did before I went up.
- His name is Walter?
Yeah.
Dude like that
shouldn't be answering the phone.
- Mr. Ryder wants to talk to you.
- Right.
Are you sure you don't have
some sort of relationship with him?
I assure you. whatever relationship
I have with him is better than yours.
Jerry. my friend. was killed
while you were talking to Ryder.
Maybe that's a question
you ask yourself instead of me.
I didn't have anything to do
with this.
But what I have in you.
Mr. Garber. is an unknown variable.
- Unknown variable?
- Right. People's lives are at stake.
- I understand that.
- Excuse me...
...if I try to get more comfortable
with you. okay?
It ain't working. but okay.
Now. with that in mind...
...would you agree
to a consensual search of your house?
Take me 40. 45 minutes
to get a warrant.
What...
Yes. okay.
Got him.
Walter Garber. right there.
No shit. look at this.
- Guy took a bribe. man.
- Yeah.
Baby!
ESU 2. this is Staley.
What's your overall status?
All positions secured.
All right.
hold your fire until instructed.
Pelham 123. can you hear me?
Yeah. loud and clear. back at you.
All right.
the mayor has agreed to pay...
...and they're getting the money
together right now.
Good.
Well. you know. you got 28 minutes.
so I advise him to make haste.
- I'm sure he will.
- So is your first name Walter?
- Excuse me?
- Your name. is it Walter?
- Yes. it is.
- Good.
What are you doing
dispatching trains?
I thought you were some sort of
MTA big shot.
I work for the MTA.
Today they put me at dispatch...
...and my bad luck.
I thought you didn't
believe in bad luck.
I said I didn't believe in fate.
Do you believe in
rigged contracts for new trains?
Look. what are
we talking about this for?
- I need to know who I'm dealing with.
- You need to know who...?
Yeah. I want to know who I'm dealing
with. I mean. are you a bad penny?
Let me explain something to you.
Being accused of something
is one thing.
Being guilty of it
is something entirely different.
Well. agreed. But you gotta
take me through this. my man.
You got to tell me from the top.
This whole train thing. Come on.
All right.
I started out in maintenance.
Platform maintenance.
track maintenance. flagman...
...conductor.
- Conductor. really?
Yeah. And then motorman.
A motorman.
How long did you do that for?
I drove them over six years.
I went to tower operations.
assistant dispatcher. dispatcher.
I finally ended up...
Yeah. you're assistant chief
transportation officer or something.
- Right?
- That's right.
And part of my job is to go out
to the manufacturers. you know...
... the people who build the trains
and bid on contracts for the trains.
Is that where you took the bribe?
The Japanese train
over the Canadian train?
I did not take a bribe. all right?
I was accused of taking a bribe.
I have not been proven guilty yet.
They haven't said yet.
I mean. they haven't decided.
Well. they got no proof. I don't care
what they decide. It doesn't matter...
Then is this
when they demoted you?
That's correct. They demoted me.
pending the outcome.
And now they're trying
to humiliate you. is that right?
Motherfuckers.
Look. I know
how these things work. man. okay?
Everything doesn't seem
to appear like what it is.
But you've gotta be
completely honest with me. man.
- Don't know what you're talking about.
- How did you do it?
I didn't. I'm innocent.
Oh. you're innocent.
No. you're talking to a Catholic.
man.
We've been over innocent before.
Okay?
Look. I've been through all this. man.
So just tell me. how did you do it?
I didn't do it.
Okay. that's it! That's fucking it!
Damn it.
- Kid. You.
- Me?
No. no. you. Up.
Get the fuck over there.
I don't know what you did
to piss him off.
Garber.
You know what I'm looking at?
- Do you know what I'm looking at?
- No. I do not.
First there's my gun. and at the end
of my gun... What's your name?
- George. Everyone calls me Geo.
- George. His friends call him Geo.
Got this '80s skateboard thing
going.
He makes it work. but it's not gonna
look too good in his casket.
Listen. Ryder. just slow down.
We haven't reached the deadline.
No. there's no fucking deadline.
man.
You just gotta tell me the truth.
- About what?
- The bribe!
- Did you take it?
- I didn't take a bribe.
Okay. you got five seconds
to save this kid's life.
I didn't do anything.
- Five...
- Just wait a second.
- Four. three...
- Wait a second!
Two...
- Fucking tell him how you did it.
- All right. okay.
- Say it.
- I took the bribe.
How much?
Thirty...
How fucking much?
Thirty-five thousand dollars.
How did you do it?
I went to Japan
to look at these trains.
It's part of my job.
I...
I don't get to vote. okay?
I just recommend.
I chose what I thought
was the best train...
...the Japanese had the best train.
and I made my recommendation.
That's before you took the bribe.
Yes.
That was the train
you were gonna pick anyway. huh?
- Yes.
- And now you're fighting for your job...
...and they're trying
to humiliate you?
No. no. no. I did what I did.
And...
And it's not. you know.
it's not the MTA's fault.
What did you spend it on?
Look. what does this
got to do with anything. huh?
What did you fucking spend it on?
I used the money for my kids.
all right?
To pay my children's tuition.
I have a 17-year-old.
I have a 19-year-old daughter.
And I used the money to pay
for their college tuition. all right?
You know what. Garber?
You're my goddamn hero.
you know that?
You got a kid here. you don't even
know him. you saved his life.
That's brave. man.
That's fucking heroic.
- Tell Garber thank you.
- Thank you. Garber.
"Thank you. Garber.
for saving my life."
Thank you. Garber.
for saving my life.
You're welcome.
Sit down.
You're just like me. Garber.
I fueled this city.
I fed it breakfast every morning.
and now we're the bad guys.
I don't think so.
I don't fucking think so!
- Hello. Therese.
- Honey. look.
There are police here. Walt.
They wanna search the house.
They said you said it was okay.
Yeah. Yeah. it's okay.
It's... Just let them in.
We got nothing to hide.
Is this about the investigation?
No. no. You watching TV?
This hostage thing.
Yeah. yeah. I'm watching it.
Well. it's just that...
I'll tell you about it
when I get home...
...but I'm in the middle of it now and
they wanna do background checks...
...on everybody involved here
from the MTA.
- That's why they're at the house.
- All right. okay. But you're okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine. Just let them in.
I'll see you when I get home.
All right. Okay. bye.
I'm sorry. Walter.
I am.
Listen. don't let this guy
bring you into his reality. all right?
That's what he wants to do.
He hurts you. you get angry.
- He's got the advantage. Understand?
- Yeah.
Just deflect. if you can.
- Okay? All right.
- All right.
I hope they don't get fucking lost.
Fuck me! Ten-million bucks.
The joke is.
say we dipped in. took some?
Bad guys would count it.
come up short. probably kill us.
No shit.
Geo. what the fuck's happening?
Geo. Geo. what's going on?
Geo.
I'm a fucking hostage.
Listen to me.
Stream it on our site. Call the news.
Shit.
Hey.
We've gotta do something.
They're gonna kill us.
You got a plan?
I thought you'd have one.
Because I'm some
tough-looking black guy?
I saw that ring on your finger.
That was a long time ago.
- Okay?
- My husband had one just like it.
A severe sell-off underway...
... the Dow is down 450 points
in very heavy trading...
... as Wall Street reacts
to the terrorist attack...
... of the New York City
subway system.
- How's my hair look?
- Fine. You ready to make a statement?
When I have something to tell them.
It's a leadership moment. sir.
I'm not running for re-election.
for fucking president.
I left my Rudy Giuliani suit at home.
You're being selfish.
It'll take 30 seconds to reassure them.
- Over there!
- Mr. Mayor!
- Mr. Mayor! Mr. Mayor!
- Will you be making a statement?
We're doing everything
the situation demands.
I'm not gonna speculate right now.
All right?
- Mayor. is it terrorism?
- No.
Hey.
Mayor! Are they terrorists?
All right. all right. all right!
Listen. nobody said anything
about terrorism...
...or a bomb. anything like that.
Let's stop that right now. all right?
How about your divorce? Care
to speculate how that's going?
Your divorce. sir.
Been a lot of talk in the news
lately...
...that you have extramarital problems.
Your divorce. sir!
Put it on channel 15.
We got a girl in Brooklyn watching it
on her boyfriend's computer.
- It's on the damn Internet.
- What?
Hold on.
- Son of a bitch.
- That's Ramos. isn't it?
That's Phil Ramos.
- Yes. it is.
- Who's Phil Ramos?
He was a motorman. He killed a
couple of passengers 10 years ago?
High on cough syrup. ran into the
platform. went to jail for manslaughter.
Phil Ramos. I want everything.
Prison time. known associates. the
works. Looks like it's from the floor.
- Should the Internet be working there?
- No. No way.
Maybe that's how he knows about you.
He Googled you.
Or maybe Ramos told him.
who knows?
Goddamn. it's the mayor.
Hello. Your Honor.
Do me a favor.
forget about those guys.
Easy for you to say.
You rather be
one of those hostages?
No.
Listen up. I'll give you a crash course
on hostage negotiating.
We're like rodeo clowns.
We keep the bull from focusing on
what he'd like to do. Which is what?
- Kill a cowboy.
- Exactly.
Now. he's got his deadline.
You slow things down.
Preservation of life. That's our mission.
Guy's already proven he's serious.
Next deadline's gonna give
a chance again.
- How do we deal with that?
- Get the money there on time.
If we don't. we pretend
the deadline doesn't exist...
...talk through it. we buy time.
get movement.
- Movement?
- That's right.
Contradicts himself. inconsistency in
his demand. you got some movement.
- Right.
- All right. let's go out there.
This was the scene
moments ago...
... outside the Rail Control Center
in Midtown.
I'm not gonna speculate right now.
That is a beautiful suit
he's got there.
Can't get it out of my head.
I'm gonna die today.
Visualization's a very powerful thing.
You keep thinking it. you never know.
Please let it be me
who drops this motherfucker.
Hey. Garber. You there. buddy?
Yeah. I'm here.
A little birdie told me
the mayor walked in.
Can I talk to him?
- Can he hear me?
- How does he know I'm here?
- Does he have a camera in here?
- Can he hear me?
We can. we can. we can...
We can all hear you here. Yes.
Okay. good. So tell him...
Tell him I wanna make him a deal.
Tell him I'll make him a deal
right now.
Okay. all right.
Well. come on. speak up.
Mr. Mayor.
You're talking to your constituents.
We got a train full
of registered voters. Don't you care?
Don't you care about your voters?
This is not a good idea.
Don't talk. Don't engage with him.
I know what I'm doing.
I've been doing this a long time.
Come on. buddy. speak up.
You gotta hit the blue button there.
Your Honor.
Yes. this is the mayor.
Hey. Good to meet you. man.
And listen. tell me this. is this true?
I read that you make. like...
... one dollar a year to be a mayor
of New York. is that true?
Yes. but at least it's honest work.
After taxes that's. like.
87 cents. isn't it?
Yes.
Don't bullshit me. man.
It would take. like. 3000 years
to pay off that suit that you're wearing.
What do you got. 20. 30 million
dollars or something like that?
You don't get that without screwing
someone. screwing everyone.
I'm sure your wife knows
something about that.
You said you had a deal for me.
Yeah. I do.
I wanna make you a deal.
I wanna tell you
you could come down here...
...and I will trade you for all these
passengers in the train. how's that?
Okay. you could save the lives
of 17 New Yorkers.
Now. that's a good deal.
What do you think?
Give us a moment.
Okay.
I'll give you a moment.
You turn this into a circus.
gonna get someone killed.
Now. you entered his world. exit it.
Okay. time's up. What's the deal?
It's a nice offer. but I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to decline.
Good. Because if you begged me.
I wouldn't give you that deal. man.
You think anyone cares about
a philandering asshole like you?
New York would love me to
pull the fucking trigger on you.
Hey. Garber. This is the... This is
the guy that's trying to get rid of you.
- Keep talking.
- Do you believe this shit?
- Calm...
- You don't think he...
...broke the same rules
we broke?
- He knows it. I know it.
- Calm him down.
- All right...
- He can eat shit.
- Calm him down.
- You're...
- You're breaking up.
- He can kiss my ass!
I like the deal.
It's a good deal. but...
Fuck you. Mr. Mayor!
Now. I want my fucking money now!
You understand me? Now!
- Just tell him the money's on the way.
- The money's on the way.
Because he's. like.
a used-car salesman. this asshole.
He can lick my bunghole.
motherfucker!
One mistake
and everyone has something to say.
Was she worth it?
Yes. You have nine minutes.
How are you gonna get the money?
They're shutting down every
intersection here to Brooklyn.
Phil Ramos. male. Hispanic. 39.
Sentenced two to four years
for manslaughter...
...paroled last month from Clinton.
His PO. Justafarro. says he's
living in a halfway house in Queens.
He's not an absconder. he made his
appearances. his piss has been clean.
But he was a no-show at work today.
He didn't call in. nothing.
He knows the system.
The perfect place in the subway
to stop the train.
He's been out a month.
This wasn't planned in three weeks.
Find out Ramos's cellmates.
who worked in the laundry with him.
Call lists. visitors lists ASAP.
105 North Avenue.
- Shit! Look out!
- Shit!
The market has tumbled
nearly 7 percent...
... as investors continue
to react to events...
They just came off the bridge.
Why didn't we send
a helicopter for the money?
Now remember what I said
about talking through deadlines.
We better have a plan B in case
the money isn't there on the dot.
Put him on his heels.
He knows things.
- We know things too. right?
- Right.
Ask him about Phil Ramos. All right?
Just get him talking.
You can do it.
- Hey. Ryder.
- The money here yet?
On the way.
Then what the fuck
are you calling me for?
Actually. I just called to talk.
Oh. yeah?
What do you wanna talk about?
You said that
being in the motorman's cab...
...was a little like
being in a confessional. right?
Yeah?
I was thinking maybe it's like
being in a prison cell too.
What are you trying to say? That
if I get caught. I'd better get used to it?
No. I'm just wondering.
Maybe you're already used to it.
I'm wondering maybe that's how
you meet a guy like Phil Ramos?
How the fuck he know that?
Why don't you tell me?
Then we'll both know.
After today's confession...
... you're gonna find your ass
in prison too.
Which is my point. I want you
to hook me up on the inside.
You know everybody. This way.
when I come up with my heist plan...
...you know. I'll cut you in.
I can see I've inspired you.
Okay. I got a story for you.
It might help you in prison.
You wanna hear it? We got a minute.
I'd like to hear a little story.
So back in the day.
when I was a high roller...
When were you ever a high roller?
I told you I fed this city breakfast.
Grits and eggs?
Something like that.
Anyway. back in the day...
...I took this chick to Iceland.
Iceland? Is that where
all the high rollers go?
Six hours from Kennedy
and the nightclub scene is...
...you know. is intense.
I thought I'd take this chick
to Iceland.
- What's her name?
- Ludvika.
She was Lithuanian.
She was an ass model.
She asked you what?
You heard of hand models?
Advertisement?
Right. she was an ass model.
She did jeans and. you know.
magazines and shit.
Anyway.
it was Fashion Week in New York...
...and I took her to Iceland.
Ludvika. Lithuanian. ass model.
Iceland. you took her to the ice.
- So what?
- Well. for 500 bucks...
... they'll take you on a dogsled ride
on a glacier.
- Dogsled?
- Yeah. And you know the old saying:
If you're not the lead dog...
...the view never changes?
- Right.
Otherwise. you're always looking at
the asshole of the dog in front of you.
Be funny in a minute
when I get to that part.
It's funny now.
And it's 8 in the morning.
we haven't been to bed yet...
... and we're tooling across
this glacier...
... and I got this hangover that's
creeping up the back of my neck...
...and guess what I'm looking at?
Obviously you're staring at the ass
of the dog in front of you.
You got it.
So this dog. out of nowhere.
just lifts its hind legs up...
...and puts them in
the harness there...
... and just takes a shit
while he's running on his front paws.
So he's dumping
and running all at the same time.
Now. that's multi-fucking-tasking
if you ask me.
Get out of here. Did it hit you?
Shit always hits you. man.
I didn't know it at the time.
but it was profound.
- Profound? You lost me.
- Yeah.
Well. you know. when I went to
prison later on. which you called...
...I had trouble going to the toilet.
You know. a privacy thing.
And I couldn't take a shit.
I was scared shitless. literally.
So you know what I thought of?
- You thought of the dog.
- That's right.
I thought if that dog could do
what it needed to do. so could I.
Saved my fucking life.
Wow. that is profound.
Keep going.
And. you know. it's...
People adapt. It's like you and I.
like today.
We didn't know how it
was gonna start.
- Wrong.
- Wrong what?
I knew exactly
how it was gonna start.
Yeah. but do you know
how it's gonna end?
- I'm tired of talking to you. Garber.
- Wait a minute.
Call me when the money comes in.
You got four minutes.
I don't know what he looks like.
but he sounds good.
Fucking talk shit.
what are you doing?
He's got a sexy voice though.
He'd be my bitch in prison.
Where are we?
Less than 10 blocks away.
We'll make it.
Fuck. look out!
Jesus.
Shit. The goddamn money car
crashed on 1 st Avenue.
Get a radio car.
put it on the motorcycles. get it there.
Watch it. Easy.
Here. lean up here.
Hey. get that last bag.
- You got 22 seconds. Garber.
- All right. we just had...
...a little problem over here. that's all.
- I don't care.
- Two minutes.
- Just tell him it's here.
- How's he gonna know?
- I don't think we should lie.
- Tell him the truth.
- No. tell him it's there.
Tell him the truth?
He's gonna make me do it.
- Ten. nine. eight. seven. six...
- Tell him the truth or lie?
- Tell him the truth.
- Tell him it's there.
- Four. three...
- Tell him it's here.
- It's here.
- Two. one.
The money's there.
it's at 42nd and Vanderbilt.
Liar! Motherfucking liar!
Seven.
- One. two. three. four. five. six. seven.
- Ryder. All right. listen.
- Lucky lady. up.
- We made a mistake.
- I think that's him. That's Ryder.
- Lucky lady. up.
- Listen to me. it was an accident.
- Keep talking.
Ryder. we made a mistake.
It's my fault.
- The car crashed.
- Tell him something!
- That's why the money's not there.
- Up!
- Wait.
- Fuck. no.
- Get up!
Get back in line!
Ryder. like one minute
it's gonna take.
Don't do this. for God's sake.
It was an accident.
- Come on.
- Wait.
It's the only plan I got.
Ryder. listen. it was an accident.
It was an accident. Ryder.
We made a mistake.
It was an accident. Ryder!
It was an accident!
Come on. motherfucker!
Oh. shit.
God!
Oh. my God.
ESU Team 1 to Sniper 1.
do you have a shot?
That's your fault.
I got an easy shot. Please advise.
- Stand by.
- Roger that.
Shit!
What the fuck happened?
Accidental discharge.
I just got bit by a fucking rat.
It's accidental discharge.
Who? Who got shot? Was it Ryder?
No. it was Ramos.
- Sergeant? The money there yet?
- What? Yes. yes.
- Are you there?
- Get in here.
Shoot any motherfucker that moves.
- That's an order!
- Shit on your orders.
Can you hear me. Ryder?
Okay.
now somebody else has to die.
Two people. maybe all of us.
Did you hear me?
I heard you. but you gotta understand.
the circumstances...
...they're different now for you.
- You gotta rethink.
- No.
You got to adapt.
No. I gave you instructions.
and you know the consequences!
I mean. don't you have a plan B?
No. plan B is enforcing plan A!
And the minute you stop believing me.
motherfucker. that's it!
I believe you. you gotta believe
and understand those cops...
...are gonna be down
and next to you any second...
Bring it. man! Let them
unload their guns. I don't care!
And what's the point of that?
What's the point?
I told you we all owe God a death.
And now it's two minutes
past the deadline. two minutes.
Which means two people.
almost three. have to go.
They have to die.
The money's there. Ryder.
Nobody else has to die.
The money's there.
I don't know what you owe God. I can
tell you. you can't pay him in cash.
You never see a U-Haul
behind a hearse. Ryder.
The Egyptians tried it. It doesn't work.
You can't take the money with you.
Ryder?
All this talk of God.
I think I need to pray.
Give me a minute.
I can do that.
You did good. Walter.
What's the reality of getting in.
ending this?
We'd have to be willing to accept
heavy casualties.
It's a hard choice. but I say make it.
New York City does not have
an acceptable casualty rate.
This is your area.
what do you suggest?
We should buy time. So far this
son of a bitch hasn't allowed us to.
This might be the first time
we got through.
Trust your man? He confessed
to a felony 20 minutes ago.
There are people down there
who are alive because of him.
Until we change the rules
or hope runs out...
...we should stick with the situation
we have now.
Do what you need to do.
Hey. Garber. you there?
- Yeah. I'm here.
- Speak up.
I'm here.
- I talked to God.
- That's good. What did he say?
He said I should trust in him.
All others. pay cash.
How soon can you get it down here?
From that station. it would take them
about five minutes to walk it down.
- No can do.
- About 10 minutes to walk it down.
No. no. no. I mean you. man.
How long would it take you
to come down here?
Don't understand.
What do you mean?
I mean you. I wanna meet you.
And if you bring it.
I know the cops aren't bringing it.
Well. you know. I don't know
how I'm gonna carry that money.
- It must weigh...
- Two-hundred and twenty pounds.
Stick it in a wheelbarrow
or something.
Why are we discussing weight?
Shouldn't you think:
- "Get the fuck out of there"?
- Okay. get the fuck out of there.
Good. that's progress.
Now. look. plan B. Your idea.
And part of plan B is you. Garber.
deliver that money...
...or I kill another hostage.
you got that?
You got seven minutes. buddy boy.
You got six minutes and 55 seconds.
check me.
Do it!
I check.
And tell that sleazebag negotiator
to call me when you've got the money.
You don't have to do this.
Finally somebody got their head
out of their ass. huh?
Hello?
Hey. how you doing. baby?
What are you doing?
What do you mean. what am I doing?
I'm watching the thing. the hostages.
They mentioned you. They said a
dispatcher was talking to the terrorists.
Yeah. yeah. they're not terrorists.
They are if they're down there
waving guns.
Right. right.
Listen. Therese. are you listening?
- I'm listening.
- Look. I'm the one that...
You're right. I was the one
that's been talking to them.
I knew it. I am so proud of you.
After everything. all this.
them trying to fire you.
Them sticking you
in a dispatch job and you...
Where are you?
I'm at a heliport.
I'm getting ready
to get on a helicopter...
...because they want me to take
the money down to the tunnel.
What? Are they crazy?
- It's real simple. There's nothing to it.
- Over there.
What it is. is he knows I'm not a cop.
so he wants me to come down...
Is it all right if I wait here?
Can I wait here?
They need me to take the money down
because they know I'm not a cop...
...and. you know. they're saying
that he might kill somebody. honey.
Well. then somebody has to die.
because you can't.
He's talking to his wife.
I understand. baby.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
- Just tell Angela at the meet...
- Let's go!
When she runs over the hurdles.
Tell her to run straight through
the hurdles.
- Just like I always tell her. okay?
- Come on. we gotta go.
You tell her yourself.
- Now. you listen to me.
- Yeah. I'm listening.
Now. you do what you have to do.
but we need milk.
So on your way home.
I want you to bring a gallon.
Of milk? Okay.
You promise.
Why do we...? Why a gallon?
Why not a half a gallon?
Just bring a gallon. A gallon.
Okay. Okay.
I can get a half a gallon.
I'll get a half a gallon.
I gotta go.
All right. thanks. guys.
Put your... Put your headset on.
You ever do anything like this before?
You know. go in unarmed?
Yeah. Two years ago. Brooklyn.
Flatbush Avenue.
I got the hostages out.
And the guy with the gun?
The guy with the gun.
didn't end well for him.
- For the guy with the gun?
- Yeah.
It's nice seeing it
from this perspective. huh?
You can see what you're fighting for.
I love you so much.
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
Well. do you love me back?
Can't really talk right now.
All you have to say is "Yes."
That's a lot less words than saying.
"I can't talk."
I'm having a really weird
fucking day.
Oh. God.
If we'd anticipated this.
we could have made a lot of money.
What kind of guy
would you expect...
...to take a model to Iceland
for the weekend?
- An ass model.
- A Wall Street guy.
He's here!
The one-hour time limit
reported earlier has expired.
We're not sure who this is. It could
be hostage negotiators or detectives.
Once we have any updates.
we'll be back to you live.
- Camonetti.
- How are you?
- Mr. Garber. Lieutenant Staley.
- Pleasure.
- You got a radio set up to the train?
- Set up right there.
You can talk to the train
or to Rail Control.
Okay. Just do what he says.
and remember everything you see.
Let's go.
So who the hell did you fuck
to get this job?
Myself. It was easier than it looked.
Yeah. fucking yourself always is.
Pelham 123. come in.
Who am I talking to?
This is Lieutenant Camonetti.
We spoke earlier.
Yeah. you're the greaseball.
What'd you do. go out for a pizza?
What's my money doing. man?
Where is it?
Mr. Garber is in the tunnel.
The money is two minutes away.
Oh. Garber. man.
That is a dependable man.
He's a good man too.
Absolutely. How about you. Ryder?
Everybody's got some good in them.
don't you think?
Is this where
you try to get through to me?
I don't think so. motherfucker.
Now I got three instructions for you.
Number one.
when this conversation is over...
...I want you to restore the power
to the whole sector.
Number two.
I want you to clear the local tracks...
...from 68th Street
down to Coney Island.
And when I say. "Clear."
I don't wanna see no cops.
I want all the lights green.
Don't trip me up with a red.
got that?
Absolutely.
And number three.
don't play games with me...
...or I'll track you down and I'll fuck you
in your greaseball ass. motherfucker!
Over and out.
Let's go.
All right.
- Know how to use one of these?
- No.
It's really simple. Okay?
Safety's on. safety's off.
On. off.
Aim at anything you don't like.
you pull the trigger.
- What if they frisk me?
- We got that covered.
- That's it?
- That's it.
It's got a false bottom.
It's gonna be this one. You got that?
- I got it.
- Good.
Don't worry about it.
Just don't fuck it up.
Okay.
We got an ID on Ryder.
Dennis Ford. He was released from
Clinton Correctional two weeks ago.
Did a nine-year stretch.
The last four on the same cell block
as Phil Ramos.
His name shows up
on an Icelandic Air passenger list...
...in September of 1998.
right after Fashion Week.
Dennis Ford. You remember?
We used his case when
he was running as an example of...
The kind of nonsense that we would
clean up if I got elected mayor. yeah.
He ran a private equity firm.
His biggest client
was the pension fund.
- He siphoned off...
- Twenty-million dollars.
He did a plea bargain for three.
The judge gave him 10.
Maybe that's why he's so pissed off.
Judge gave him 10 years because we
didn't recover all of the city's money.
Couple million unaccounted for.
Seed money.
Seed money? For what?
For today. you play the terrorist card.
you panic the market into a drop.
You know it's coming. you make
a great deal with $2 million.
- What about the hostage money?
- That's nothing...
...compared to the money you could
make. Let's get downtown to the SEC.
Check the trades.
especially the put options.
- Good luck. Garber.
- See you when you get back.
We got company.
Garber.
When you put your socks on
this morning. did you ever think...?
Turn around. let him frisk you.
I was worried about you.
I thought maybe you'd get lost...
...but then I remembered
you were a motorman. so...
These tunnels don't change much.
do they?
Just the people in them.
- Are we good?
- It's here. We're good.
All right. come on up.
Let's go.
Damn.
You're taller than I thought you'd be.
You're good-looking too.
Come on. sit down.
It's nice to meet you.
What do you weigh.
about. what. 220?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
220 on a good day.
Oh. that's Ramos.
He's what you would have called
the brains in the operation.
Dumb fuck.
So how long has it been
since you've driven one of these?
- That's why you brought me here?
- You're a motorman. right?
Once a motorman.
always a motorman.
You play your cards right.
you might get a part of the cut.
Well. this is...
It's a new train.
I'm not certified on the new trains.
Well. I got faith in you. man.
But I'm going to ask you one question.
You know. that thing when you
told your wife about the 35 K...
...how did she react?
- We gotta talk about...?
- Don't be sensitive.
- I'm not being...
- Did she freak out or what?
She wasn't happy.
but she understood.
Well. that's love. right?
No. that's marriage.
That's another thing.
You think they're gonna move
that train?
Seems like a possibility. How are we
with street-level. emergency exits?
I got a blanket.
I got radio cars and a man
at every exit from 42nd to South Ferry.
We gotta go.
Hey. Camonetti.
Fucking greaseball. man.
Hey. greaseball. speak up.
I see red. I don't see green.
What's taking so fucking long?
Blanket is not tucked in yet.
Stall him. I need two minutes.
buy me two minutes.
Haven't cleared the tracks yet.
Mr. Ryder. we'll be up and ready
in less than two minutes.
We're gonna move forward here.
okay?
We're gonna move forward.
and if we get onto a red signal...
...and the brakes trip up...
...your friend Walter Garber's
getting it in the head.
- You got it?
- Yes. sir. I got it.
Let's roll. let's roll.
Hope you were bluffing.
Yeah. I'm bluffing. man.
You gotta say what you gotta say.
You thought by coming down here.
you'd be redeemed. didn't you?
God bless you. Garber.
You're more fucked up than I am.
At least the same fucked up.
Come on. let's go. let's go. let's go.
Let's go.
She's on the move.
Put some speed on it.
He's by me. headed south.
Male. black. at the controls.
Motherfuckers.
You're playing with fire. my man.
I wanna see them green.
Turn to green or I'll put a hole
in Garber's head right now.
- Do it!
- We believe you.
We're moving as fast as we can.
- What happens if they run a red light?
- It'll trip the brakes.
Coming up on the first one.
There. that's what I'm looking for.
That's what I'm looking for.
Here he comes. right now.
Garber's driving the train.
Sniper confirmed it.
What are you saying. he's
in on it? There ain't no way.
Sniper killed Ramos.
he was their driver...
...they probably need Garber
to drive.
They get to Coney Island. they hit the
trippers and the brakes will come on.
- Is that 33rd?
- Yes. sir.
- How far to the signal?
- About a tenth of a mile.
You stop when we get there.
We're moving out. You got that?
I'm slowing down now.
Are they slowing down?
They have to.
They're coming up to a signal point.
What is that?
You're the old motorman.
you tell me.
- She stopped just below 33rd Street.
- What the hell are they doing?
Oh. jeez.
Why that little stop?
Train has to stop at signal points.
Some kind of an override?
Yep. some kind of an override.
that's right.
There we go.
Okay. let's move out. Let's go. let's go.
Roosevelt tunnel. which way?
Which way?
She's moving again.
Next stop. 28th Street.
Why that little stop. huh?
- I told you. the signal points.
- How do you know...
...they didn't set the throttle. jump?
- We got every exit covered.
There's nowhere to go.
Listen. the throttle can't be set.
It has to be held.
It's the failsafe.
it's a dead-man's switch.
Doesn't have a hand
pressing down on it...
...the train stops cold.
Believe me. they're still aboard.
It's going faster.
Emri. off the track. Come on.
Let's go!
Garber. come on.
Come on!
It's gonna derail
before it gets to Coney Island.
That's it. That's it right there.
Roosevelt tunnel.
It's a fucking train crossover.
Come on. Cross over now!
- What?
- Come on. move!
Hey!
- Fuck it. let's go!
- We gotta find him!
We don't have time! Let's go!
I love you. I fucking love you.
Geo. I fucking love you too.
Hello? Hello?
We're getting calls.
Cops on the platform
are seeing passengers...
...nobody in the motorman's booth.
- Believe me. they're still aboard.
It's all right!
As soon as we hit a red light...
...the brakes will stop it automatically.
- Yeah. but they're all green!
Four stops away.
Two stops.
Oh. Jesus. The train just stopped.
I really gotta take that piss.
There's no hijackers onboard.
just passengers.
Where was that first stop
that they made?
Near 34th.
- That's by the Roosevelt spur.
- The what?
A derelict tunnel
built under the Waldorf Hotel.
Converge everything on that area.
Throw a goddamn dragnet over it!
Hey!
Freeze!
Put your hands in the air!
Hey!
Hey. Get out. get out. get out.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Out of the... Get out of the way!
Just go. go. go.
- 911 operator.
- Hello? Hello?
- This is Walter Garber. MTA.
- How do you spell that?
Don't worry about how to spell it.
Just tell Lieutenant Camonetti...
...that Ryder is headed
to the Manhattan Bridge!
Cars everywhere. Nobody's
going anywhere for a long time.
Hey. Hey!
- Is he in there?
- No. no. no.
- No.
- Where did he go?
Brooklyn. He said he couldn't wait.
he started walking.
This fucking city!
Come on. you guys. Move out!
Ryder!
Don't move.
So is this how you thought
the day was going to end. huh?
When you put your socks on
this morning?
This make you feel better. Garber?
That make everything okay now?
No! But it's a start.
Don't move.
Don't move!
Hey!
Garber Baby boy.
I ain't going back to prison.
I don't... I don't think you got any...
Any options now or leverage.
Hey!
We all owe God a death.
I told you that.
You're wrong. Ryder.
We owe God life.
Life. And that's the life
I gave you back today.
And now you have to
give me something back.
What are you talking about?
You got a gun in your hand.
I want you to use it. Shoot me.
No. shoot me before they shoot me.
or I'm gonna kill you.
I will shoot you.
I don't want to. but I will.
- Hey!
- I thought you cared.
- No!
- You said:
"Ryder. Ryder.
don't you have anyone who cares?"
I thought that was you.
- Come on. man. pay it back.
- I'm not gonna shoot you.
I'm gonna give you 10.
then deal's off.
I got a gun. I'm gonna use it.
I'm gonna take your life back.
- Hey!
- Come on. man!
Ten. nine. eight. seven. six. five...
You gonna take this down to zero?
Come on. motherfucker. shoot me!
I am not going to shoot you!
Five. four. Come on.
- Hey!
- Three.
Police. drop your weapon!
I'm disappointed in you. Two.
You're my goddamn hero.
Drop your weapon!
Mr. Garber.
- Interesting day. huh?
- Yes. sir.
You know. just about every day
I make a speech...
...and it starts with:
"I'd like to thank you on behalf of
the city of New York." blah. blah. blah.
And I never know
who I'm thanking or why.
But you...
...did a hell of a thing today.
You went to bat
for the city of New York.
And on behalf of me.
I'd like to thank you.
Well. you're welcome.
I mean. it's been an amazing day.
Everybody's thanking me all day.
but I appreciate it. You're welcome.
And I want you to know...
...that tomorrow. the city of New York
is going to go to bat for you.
In a big way. You understand?
Yes. sir.
And this city
has a very good batting average.
- I appreciate it.
- All right.
I'm gonna get home.
Oh. take my car.
- No. no. I'll take...
- Put the siren on and everything.
- There's a siren on there?
- Yes.
No. I'll take the subway.
But I appreciate it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know. me. subway all my life.
I get home faster than you anyway.
Not you. but. you know.
everybody else.
But thank you. sir.
You a Yankee fan?
No. Well. yes. Yes. of course.
Yeah. right.
Stand clear of the closing doors.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm